Nagarjuna BellamKonda () Featured

SQL Developer seeking assignments in Software Development, Application
Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement
Gathering, System Analysis, Solution Architecture, SSRS, SSIS, MS SQL Server, C#, Core
Java, HTML, CSS, Database Management



Current Designation: SQL Developer Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Altruista health Solutions Private Limited Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: SQL Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Program

Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Solution Architecture, SSRS, SSIS, MS SQL

Server, C#, Core Java, HTML, CSS, Database Management

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Over 7+ years of SQL Development experience with in-depth knowledge of indexes, joins, views and functions. Well versed in creating stored procedures, user defined functions, derived tables, and common table expressions (CTEs) and triggers and also Importing/Exporting Data from Excel to SQL Server Good Knowledge in SQL and BIDS Developer.

Equally effective working independently or as part of a team.

Analytical thinking and problem-solving skills very determined and diplomatic work ethics.

Work Experience

Altruista health Solutions Private Limited as SQL Developer Dec 2018 to Till Date

- Over 7+ years of experience in application design, development &maintenance on SQL Server 2008R2/2012/2014.
- * Proficient in report generation using SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS) from relational database.
- * Expert in transforming complex business logic into database design & maintaining it by using SQL tools like stored procedure, user define function, views and T-SQL scripting.
- * Expertise in Importing/Exporting Data from Excel to SQL Server...
- * Experience in Optimizing queries and design indexes
- * Proficiency in analyzing query plans using extended stored procedures, managing indexes and locks, troubleshooting

Launchship Technology Solutions Private Limited as SQL Developer Jan 2017 to Dec 2018

Dhanush InfoTech Pvt Ltd as SQL Developer Jul 2013 to Dec 2016

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2012

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
MS SQL Server 2008R2/2012, Oracle	
C#, Core JAVA	
html/css	
Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint	
SSRS	
sql server management studio	
Win XP, windows 7/8 and Linux	
html/css	
Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint	
SSRS	
sql server management studio	
Win XP, windows 7/8 and Linux	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english	Proficient			
telugu	Expert			
hindi	Beginner			

Projects

Project Title: Smart Track

Client: Sunturst

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jan 2017 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: A web-based HCM application that acts as a mechanism for business to manage and procure staffing services temporary, and, in some cases, permanent placement services as well as outside contract or contingent labour.

Its a consolidated solution to integrate, migrate and maintain the contingent worker information of clients across globe. It manages worker data right from screening until release from project, Managing workers time sheets, expenses and invoices.

Project Title: Learning Management System

Client: Ministry of Finance

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2012 - Jun 2015

Project Location: kenya Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Skill Used: SQL Server, ssrs

Role Description: Worked on developing Tables, Indexes, Views, Creating complex stored procedures and user defined

Functions

Project Details: Learning Management System (LMS) is designed to provide a platform for online courses. The inbuilt tools of an LMS are user friendly in catering to the needs of different levels and types of users. The users like employees with

technical qualification, non technical managers and learners (students) can avail the services from the Learning Management System. The solutions offered by LMS are easy to comprehend and simple to employ. The main modules involved in LMS are Cities, departments, Locations, States, Districts etc, Creation of Students, Trainers, Courses, Course Schedules, Assessments, Material Uploads, Archive Data, Reports.

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - non-creamy Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time